healthdirectorymoz.com 2012-10-05

# Health Information Directory | Medical Websites & Fitness Resources- Privacy

### Privacy Policy:

#### Information Collected and Stored Automatically

We do **not** collect personal information about you when you visit our Web sites unless you choose to provide that information to us.

When you visit an Healthdirectorymoz web site, we may store some or all of the following: the Internet address from which you access the web site, date and time, the Internet address of the web site from which you linked to our site, the name of the file or words you searched, items clicked on a page, and the browser and operating system used.

This information is used to measure the number of visitors to the various sections of our site and identify system performance or problem areas. We also use this information to help us expand the coverage of the site, to analyze patterns of usage, and to make the site more useful.

However, this information is **not** used for associating search terms or patterns of site navigation with individual users. Healthdirectorymoz periodically deletes its Web logs. On occasion, Healthdirectorymoz may provide this information to third party entities it contracts with for the purposes of research analysis.

#### Cookies

A "cookie" is a small file that a Web site transfers to your computer's hard disk allowing our server to "remember" specific information about your session. While visiting certain Healthdirectorymoz sites you may occasionally encounter a Web page that employs cookies to make it easier to use the dynamic features of these Web pages. 

The cookie and the information about your session will be destroyed automatically shortly after you close your browser-it is not permanently stored on your computer. You can set your browser to disable cookies or prompt you before a cookie is accepted.

We use third-party advertising companies like Google adsense to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

#### Personally Provided Information

If you choose to provide us with personal information by sending an email, or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it through our Web site, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us provide you with information or material that you request.

If provided, personally identifiable information is maintained in a database that is regularly purged. Third party contractors may have access to this information in order to provide an initial response to your question or comment.

These contractors are held to strict policies to safeguard the information and provide the same level of privacy protection as guaranteed by Healthdirectorymoz. On occasion, we may conduct a study concerning the types of questions sent to us. These studies help us to improve our Web sites in order to make them more responsive to the needs of our users. We do not give, share, sell, or transfer any personal information to a third party unless required by law.

#### Links to Other Sites

Most Healthdirectorymoz listed Web sites, such as MedlinePlus, provide links to other Internet sites that provide health information. Once you link to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.

#### Security

A team of professionals maintains this site. For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we use software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. 

HealthDirectoryMoz abides the legal requirements of medical/health information privacy that apply in the U.S. Causing intentional damage to our computer systems is a violation of U.S. law and is subject to criminal prosecution in court of Law. In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations, and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.

This Page is Last Updated: 7th April 2009.
